let MCQS = [{
    question: "Which 3 levels in OSI Model are usually implemented in the software within the operating system?",
    choice1: "Application, Presentation, Session  ",
    choice2: "Data Link, Transport, Application  ",
    choice3: "Transport, Session, Presentation  ",
    choice4: "All of them",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Which of these protocols reside in Layer 3 - Network in the OSI Model?",
    choice1: "TCP and IPSec",
    choice2: "IP and IPSec  ",
    choice3: "IP and TCP",
    choice4: "only TCP",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "A netmask can be represented by which two ways",
    choice1: "Decimal Numbers (Netmask: 255.255.255.0) and Slash Notation (80.212.212.50/32)  ",
    choice2: "Pound Notation (80.2012.212.50#24) and Decimal Numbers (Netmask: 255.255.255.0)  ",
    choice3: "Slash Notation (80.212.212.50/32) and Pound Notation (80.2012.212.50#24)",
    choice4: "Port Notation ( 255.232.2323270#)",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "What is spoofing?",
    choice1: "Falsifying data, making something appear different than they really are  ",
    choice2: "A way server hides from attacks, a defensive mechanics",
    choice3: "A way of terminating a 3-way handshake connection",
    choice4: "A way of terminating a 4-way handshake connection",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "What is Zero-Trust architecture?",
    choice1: "A network where all systems/resources need explicit access to be able to communicate  ",
    choice2: "A network where only some resources/devices are trusted",
    choice3: "A network where we do not trust public network(internet), but we trust local network",
    choice4: "a random network",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "ARP Scanning can only be used to identify hosts/systems on the LAN",
    choice1: "False",
    choice2: "True",
    choice3: "EH",
    choice4: "I dont know",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "What is IDOR?",
    choice1: "I Do Order Ranch",
    choice2: "Invalid Data or Reference  ",
    choice3: "Insecure Direct Object Reference  ",
    choice4: "Insecure Door or Room",
    answer: 2
},{
               question: "What is SQL injection?.",
    choice1: "Inject good code to the database server",
    choice2: "It is used to inject malicious code to a database server, through a query  ",
    choice3: "It is used in Buffer Overflow attacks to overwrite memory  ",
    choice4: "It is used to spoof or inject false headers in a HTTP request",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "What is CSP - Content Security Policy? ",
    choice1: "A strict way of sanitizing user input on a website",
    choice2: "A strict way of controlling where javacsript is allowed to be executed from  ",
    choice3: "TLS encryption between server and client",
    choice4: "Command and Control place",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Which order of security protocols is correct, going from least to most secure?",
    choice1: "WPA, WEP, WPA2, WPA4",
    choice2: "WPA, WEP, WPA2, WPA3",
    choice3: "WPA, WEP, WPA2, WPA3",
    choice4: "WEP, WPA, WPA2, WPA3  ",
    answer: 3
}];